This style is collar is called a notched collar with a blanket stitch.
Now, we have seen many many times the notched collar aspect of it comes in here and here.
Remember, this is all one piece when it is sewn together because you are going to have it sewn together here.
The blanket stitch comes from what you do as an after-treatment.
The blanket stitch is going to be along every edge of your fabric, every outer edge.
And, think about those, a blanket is stitch is what it sounds like.
It is stitching that is done on, like say you have one of those fleece blankets you watch TV on your couch with.
A blanket stitch, look at the end of that blanket, it curves and loops up into it.
You will see, if you are looking at it flat on, you will see from this top looking at it that it curves like that.
And then, from the side, you will also see that there is a stitch right there preventing the fraying.
You cannot see that because that would be like a cross-section.
But, that is the type of stitch used all along the outer edges to have it be a notched collar with a blanket stitch.